

Hi! I'm Kunal Khurana, a soil physicist with more than 10 years of working experience in agronomy, soil fertility, and plant nutrition. I gained this experience by working at different geographic locations of the world on diverse projects with different experts. I am particularly passionate about working with AI and machine learning professionals to fight against climate change by storing more amount of C in the soil and saving precious water.

Education

- 2022 Génie et Science Appliquées Cégep du Vieux Montréal, CA
- 2021 Francisation et Intégration au Milieu Québécois Université Laval, CA
- 2016 Master's in Soil Science Punjab Agricultural University, IN
- 2013 Bachelor's in Agriculture Punjabi University Patiala, IN

Work Experience

September 2022 – March 2023 Research Assistant, Mcgill University

September 2020 – November 2020 Freelance Translator, Cerda

January 2019 – August 2019 | Research Assistant, Université Laval

October 2016 - March 2017 Research Assistant, Punjab Agricultural University

Let's Connect!

One of my greatest motivations for creating online content is to engage with fascinating individuals from all over the world. If you're interested in having a chat, feel free to reach out to me. I would love to hear from you!